Bubble, I demand an apology!
Huh? What for?
You know exactly the reason.
I know you do!
Is it because I killed you?
No! I don't care about that.
It's because you didn't give me IMMUNITY!
What? That's it? Sorry, Flower,
but I don't think I'll apologize for that!
You have to!
Bubble, I-I'll apologize for you.
F- uh, Flower, Bubble is sincerely sorry
for not giving you immunity.
I-I guess that's adequate.
OMG, Leafy! Why did you do that?
I thought you hated me!
Well, I decided a little argument
shouldn't end our friendship.
Oh.
So let's be friends again!
Leafy, we're friends, and then we're not,
and then we're friends, and then we're not!
Th-this doesn't seem like a very stable friendship.
Oh, so now you don't want to be friends!
- Oh?
- Well, I guess I'd rather be with Firey!
At least he appreciates my presence.
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
You know, Firey, I've never been
in a Ferris Wheel before.
Wait till you get to the fun, special part!
Ooh! Special?
You go through a waterfall!
You're... you're allergic to water.
Yeah, I replaced with a lavafall.
Uhh...
Heh, heh, heh! Isn't this great?
No! Get me outta this thing!
Oh my gosh. Leafy, just calm
down and enjoy the ride!
Ahhhh!
When are we gonna do Cake at Stake?
Right now.
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now ♪
♪ But we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake at Stake ♪
Oh my gosh! It's a bug!
I-is it gone?
Hey, wait! Where's Leafy?
She died in the ferris wheel.
Yeah, I-I know that. But won't the
Master Recovery Center create her again?
We had to sell the recovery
centers because of budget cuts.
- You didn't! You couldn't have!
- Wanna bet?
Actually I do.
How much?
My life's earnings.
Well, it turns out that we
actually did sell them,
so thanks for the money.
So wait, you really sold the recovery centers?
You mean Leafy's never coming back?!
Yep. Can we move on now?
No! I want Leafy back!
Whatever. Be quiet. Now we really have to get going.
I agree, let's get to the elimination!
We have something else to get to first.
Really? What?
You seriously don't remember?
Sorry. Bubbles don't have brains. Give me a hint!
It has to do with the cancellation of BFDI.
Hmm... I give up. Tell me!
If the number of votes go down yet again,
BFDI will be cancelled.
Oh my gosh! I hope that doesn't happen!
Let's find out.
This suspense is KILLING me!
Hey guys! For a prank,
place an Announcer Recovery Center
next to a trampoline.
Then throw Spongy onto the trampoline.
After that, kill the Announcer!
It's a fun, easy way to create the ultimate prank!
Voiceover:
This program, was brought to you by
Blocky's Funny Doings International.
Please donate money to the
No More Advertisements Foundation
to prevent ads like these
from appearing in TV Shows.
We think ads are boring, frustrating,
disgusting and irritating.
Don't you too?!
If you donate one dollar,
you'll get a bumper sticker.
Donate five dollars and you'll
receive our subscription magazine
which includes loads of
information on latest products.
Donate a hundred dollars, and we'll put your name
in our next movie called "The Fight Against Commercials."
Go check that one out, too!
It's time to end advertisements.
Huh?
I'm sorry guys, but we got fewer
votes than last time, again. BFDI is cancelled.
So, who wins Dream Island?
No one does.
No way! This is unacceptable!
Why not?
Because I want Dream Island!
Well, too bad, and I don't think
you deserve it anyway.
Grrr!
What did you just throw on me?
Uh, I don't know! Why does it matter?
I think they're bug eggs.
Uh...
Oh my Gardener!
We have to run away people,
they'll eat us alive!
Everyone:
Ahhhh!
- What did you hear?
- Uhh... I-I  can't exactly tell what's going on right now,
but I did hear him say that BFDI was cancelled.
Oh my gosh! That's great!
How so?
Well, if BFDI is over, that
means we should be released!
Huh, that's true.
Pen's right, I can hear footsteps right now!
Wow, I can't wait!
Oh my Bubble Blower, all the losers are dead!
We have to keep going!
Recommended Characters:
Ahhhhhh!
Everyone:
Ahhhhh!
What do we do about that canyon?
Jump over it!
Gah!
Yes! I'm gonna make it!
Flower:
Ahhhhh!
Hey Firey, try burning the bugs.
That won't work.
Just try!
G-geh...
Uh oh.
Oh no, Firey's been eaten!
Just keep going.
It's not killing all of them!
Of course not, I built them to be strong.
Wait, YOU built the bugs?
Oops, forget I said anything.
I can't believe-
I have to keep my secrets.
Well, I guess it's time to do this.
Umm. I'm not sure what to do now,
because all of the contestants are gone.
David:
Aw, seriously?!
Except for David of course,
because he's immune to bugs.
Hey, I have a David Cloner.
I decided to not cancel BFDI.
David:
Aw, seriously?
The cake this time is a red velvet cake.
David:
Aw, seriously?
It was recommended by "TotalDramaIsland5543."
David:
Aw, seriously?
Go subscribe to his or her channel.
David:
Aw, seriously?
There are 3 slices of cake.
David:
Aw, seriously?
3 contestants are safe and will get cake.
David:
Aw, seriously?
1 contestant will be eliminated.
David:
Aw, seriously?
Bubble had immunity, so she is safe.
Out of the 735 votes, Firey got only 86,
so he's also safe.
David:
Aw, seriously?
Now it's down to Flower and Leafy.
Announcer:
Leafy is safe with 125 votes.
Aw, seriously?
And Flower is eliminated with a record of 524 votes.
What? No way!
Oh my gosh, how did you people come back?
We faked our deaths, obviously.
Whatever.
Announcer:
Flower, you're the first and last person to
be eliminated before the finale.
- You, Flower, are out with four votes.
- Grrrr!
Ahhhhh!
Spongy...
Ahhhhhh!
...is eliminated at 4 votes.
Ahh...
Blocky...
Ahhhhh!
...is eliminated at 6 votes.
Ahh...
Ahhhhh!
- Woody...
- Ahh...
...is eliminated at 9 votes.
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhhhhhhh!
Goodbye, Pin.
I use my Win Token!
Announcer:
Too late!
But I'm the team leader! You can't do that!
Oh no!
Eraser, you need a heroic leader like ME!
And Needy...
...is at 12 votes.
Yeah but... Needle, why don't
you like being called "Needy?"
Needy-
Teardrop, it's time to say goodbye.
Goodbye, Golf Ball, or GBGB for short.
Hyuck Hyuck, that's so hilare!
Now my chances of winning
went from 7.143%, to 0.000%!
Coiny, it looks like it's the end for you.
Announcer:
Snowball, I'm sorry to tell you that
you've been eliminated with a record of 47 votes.
Grrrr!
NOOOOO...
...OOOOOO-
No, Match, no! You've been eliminated!
OMG, I know it's so, like, hard,
but you got to keep, like, like, going!
You got to win this for like, like,
like, like, the both of us!
Eraser, goodbye.
Pen will be eliminated.
Blocky, I'm sorry, but you received 112 votes.
That's enough to eliminate you, again.
No! You can't eliminate me!
I-I'm like the star of the show!
Tennis Ball is eliminated.
Tennis Ball:
Ahhhhh!
Announcer:
You received 259 votes, which is the most ever.
You are eliminated.
What?! This machine thingy must be broken!
David is eliminated.
Aw, seriously?
Ice Cube, you have been eliminated.
Ahhhh!
And Rocky is eliminated!
- Spongy,
- Bwuh?
with a record of 432 votes,
you have been eliminated, again.
Well, I am not gonna be eliminated!
I've got my mirror!
Ha!
Why is there a bush here?
It's so bright!
Hah!
Eliminated Contestants:
Yeah!
Ahhhhh!
Oh no, not here again!
So now we have our 3 finalists:
Bubble, Firey and Leafy.
Vote who you want to win by commenting on this video.
I forgot to give you rewards.
Huh?
Rewards for getting into the Final 3.
Another reward? I love rewards!
So, what are the rewards?
Anything you ask for.
Anything?
Absolutely everything.
Well, I wish for world peace!
Wish granted.
But y-you didn't do anything!
I think the world is peaceful enough.
Moving on, Bubble.
I want some yoylecake!
Ooh, Sorry, Bubble, but that doesn't fit our budget.
Wish denied, onto Firey.
I want my life's earnings back!
Sorry, I already spent it.
On what?
Your new recovery centers.
Wow, thanks! Wait, you didn't buy these
because you care about us, did you?
Nope.
Gasp! Then why'd you do it?!
So I can do this,
and this,
and this.
What's this?